A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1976-1985.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and subject files of the Secretary of Administration and Finance,
1976-1985.
The Library of Virginia
32423, 32621, 32883, 32968, 33039
Virginia. Secretary of Administration and Finance.
40 cu. ft.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Office of the Secretary of Administration and the Office of the Secretary of Finance were created as two separate secretariats in 1972, but were combined into one secretariat in 1976. The two secretariats were again split into two separate entities in 1984.
Secretaries of Administration and Finance include: Maurice B. Rowe, 1976-1978; Charles Walker, 1978-1981; Stuart Connock, 1981-1982; and Wayne F. Anderson, 1982-1984.
Scope and Content
This series includes the incoming and outgoing correspondence and memoranda of the Secretary of Administration and Finance, as well as subject files. These records document the planning, development and establishment of policies and procedures of the secretariat and its assigned agencies.
Files may include correspondence, articles, brochures, legislation, manuals, meeting records, notes, programs, publications, regulations, reports, and studies.
Alphabetical.
Acquisition Information
Accession 32423 was transferred by the Virginia Secretary of Administration, June 24, 1985.
Accession 32621 was transferred by the Virginia Secretary of Finance, January 16, 1986.
Accession 32883 was transferred by the Virginia Secretary of Finance, December 30, 1986.
Accession 32968 was transferred by the Virginia Secretary of Finance, April 21, 1987.
Accession 33039 was transferred by the Virginia Secretary of Finance, XX
Contents List
- Correspondence and subject files, 1973-1984 (Accession 32423)., Extent: 9 cubic feet (9 boxes)
  - A-95 Process, 1982-1983. (Box 1)
  - Administration and Finance data solicited by Central Agencies Study, 1980-1981. (Box 1)
  - Administration and Finance staff, 1975-1982. (Box 1)
  - Alexandria Seaport Foundation, 1984. (Box 1)
  - Audit Specifications for Counties, Cities and Towns, 1983. (Box 1)
  - Brunswick County, 1983. (Box 1)
  - Computer Services - Collocation, 1983-1984. (Box 1)
  - Computer Services - Personnel, 1982-1984. (Box 1)
  - Conflict of Interest Act, 1979-1984. (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Duplication and Undue Competition Study - Secretarial Action Plan, 1981-1982. (Box 1)
  - Developmental Disabilities Planning Council, 1980-1981. (Box 1)
  - Ellerbe Architects and Engineers, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Energy Issues, 1982-1983. (Box 2)
  - Executive Manpower Control Program, 1981-1983. (Box 2)
  - Executive Agreements - Computer Services, 1982-1983. (Box 2)
  - Executive Agreements - Management Analysis and System Development, 1982-1984. (Box 2)
  - Executive Agreements - Telecommunications, 1982-1984. (Box 2)
  - Executive Incentive Awards, 1980-1983. (Box 2)
  - Executive Salary Plan, 1980-1982. (Box 2)
  - Executive Salary Study, 1978-1981. (Box 2)
  - Exemption Requests - Commerce and Resource, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Exemption Requests - Human Resources, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Exemption Requests - Public Safety, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Exemption Requests - Transportation, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Fair Insurance Practices Act, 1983. (Box 2)
  - Federalism, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Fund Revenue / Collections, 1981-1984. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Charges on State Property, 1979-1984. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Construction Management (Design/Build/Replan), 1980-1983. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Energy Conservation, 1981-1984. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Leasing Procedures, 1981. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Mail Messenger Service, 1980. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Office of Risk Management, 1980-1982. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Procurement Law Study, 1980. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Procurement Law Study; Vendor's Manual; Agency Procurement Manual, 1979-1983. (Box 3)
  - General Services - Procurement Law Study, 1980. (Box 4)
  - Information Strategies for the 80's (Virginia), 1982-1983. (Box 4)
  - Information Technology - Task Force information, 1982-1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - Accounts, Dept. of, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - Commonwealth, Secretary of, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - Elections, Board of, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - Computer Services, Dept. of, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - Employee Relations Counselors, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - General Services, Dept. of, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - Taxation, Dept. of, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - Teasury, Dept. of, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Administration and Finance Proposals - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Lease Purchase, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HB 30 (Aid to Localities), 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HB 519 (Virginia Supplemental Retirement System), 1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HB 669 (Tax on Advertising Inserts), 1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HB 686 (Funding for Constitutional Officers), 1982. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HB 688 (Unclaimed Property), 1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HB 755 (Establishment of State Lottery), 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HB 844 (Deferred Compensation), 1984. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HB 988 (Virginia Supplemental Retirement System), 1984. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HJR 8 (Self-Insurance for Workman's Compensation), 1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HJR 83 (Efficiency of the General Assembly), 1984. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HJR 105 (Study of Locan Mandates), 1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - HJR 117 (Status of State and Local Public Safety Employees), 1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - Item 44 (Indigent Health Care), 1982. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - SB 14 (Local Land Use Controls), 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - SB 224 (Assessment of Railroad Tax), 1983-1984. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - SJR 38 (Use of Corrections for Printing), 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - SJR 42 (Health Care Benefits), 1982. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - SJR 47 (Unemployment Compensation Trust Fund), 1982-1983. (Box 5)
  - Legislation - SJR 75 (Rolling Stock Tax), 1983. (Box 5)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of (DIT), 1981-1984. (Box 6)
  - National Governors' Association - Annual Winter Meeting, 1984 Feb 26. (Box 6)
  - National Governors' Association - Annual Meeting, 1983 July 31-Aug 2. (Box 6)
  - National Governors' Association - Staff Advisory Council meeting, 1983 June 15. (Box 6)
  - National Governors' Association - Staff Advisory Council meeting, 1983 Feb 10. (Box 6)
  - National Governors' Association - Staff Advisory Council meeting, 1982 Nov 16. (Box 6)
  - National Governors' Association - Staff Advisory Council meeting, 1982 Aug 8. (Box 6)
  - National Governors' Association - Staff Advisory Council meeting, 1982 May 10. (Box 6)
  - National Institute for Dispute Resolution, 1984. (Box 6)
  - Occoquan, Town of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Affirmative Action in Higher Education Institutions, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Deferred Compensation, 1980-1983. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Compensation Policies, 1981-1983. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Consolidated Higher Education Salary Authority, 1980-1981. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Disability Insurance, 1981. (Box 6)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - EEO Committee, 1980-1982. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - EEO Training Session, 1983. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Executive Development Institute, 1981-1983. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Health Insurance / Health Care Benefits, 1983. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Intergovernmental Personnel Act, 1980-1981. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Layoff Policy, 1981-1982. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Missed Opportunities Report, 1982. (Box 7)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Qualifications Standards, 1980. (Box 8)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Standards of Conduct, 1978-1980. (Box 8)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - Study on Limiting the Number of State Employees (John C. Pignato), 1981. (Box 8)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - TIAA/CREF, 1981-1983. (Box 8)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of - University Compentation Plans, 1980-1981. (Box 8)
  - Productivity Reports and Projects, 1978-1981. (Box 8)
  - Register of Regulation, Virginia, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Regulatory Reform, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - State Information Committee, 1981-1984. (Box 8)
  - State Information Committee, 1973-1979. (Box 9)
  - St. Julien's Property (Chesapeake and Portsmouth), 1982. (Box 9)
  - Telecommunications Division, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Unemployment Insurance Study, 1978-1982. (Box 9)
  - Unemployement Compensation, 1979-1980. (Box 9)
  - Vendors, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Virginia Innovative Group, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Virginia Municipal League, 1980-1984. (Box 9)
  - Winchester (Va.), 1980-1983. (Box 9)
  - We Have It Made In Virginia, 1984. (Box 9)
- Correspondence and subject files, 1978-1983 (Accession 32621)., Extent: 13 cubic feet (13 boxes)
  - Individual Income Tax Study, 1978. (Box 1)
  - Administration and Finance Studies, 1978. (Box 1)
  - Tax and Expenditure Limitations, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Financial Policy Task Force, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Productivity Improvement, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Self Insurance Plan - State Motor Vehicles, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Bank Stock Tax Study, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Procurement Law Study, 1979-1980. (Box 1)
  - Gifts, Grants and Donations Policy, 1979-1980. (Box 1)
  - Workmen's Compensation Insurance, 1979-1980. (Box 1)
  - Manpower Utilization Plan, 1979. (Box 1)
  - Manpower Utilization Plan, 1980. (Box 1)
  - Population Projects for Virginia (1980-2000), 1980. (Box 1)
  - Guidelines - Deputy Sheriff Compensation, 1980. (Box 1)
  - Local Government Investment - Pool Act, 1980. (Box 1)
  - Uniform Accident Prevention / Safety Program - Delinquency Study, 1980. (Box 1)
  - Program Monitoring Task Force, 1980-1981. (Box 1)
  - Internal Auditing, 1979-1980. (Box 1)
  - Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Revenue Procedure 80-55 IRS, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Layoff Policy, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Redistricting / Reapportionment, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Set-Off Debt Collection Act - Implementation, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Highway Taxation Policy, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Court Service Units, 1981-1982. (Box 1)
  - Crocklin, Edwin - Consultant, 1980-1982. (Box 1)
  - Direct Deposit, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Debt Set-Off Act, 1982-1984. (Box 2)
  - Duplication and Undue Competition Study, 1982-1983. (Box 2)
  - Reveneu Estimates (1984-1986), 1983. (Box 2)
  - Commonwealth Database, 1979-1982. (Box 2)
  - Commonwealth Database, 1980-1981. (Box 2)
  - Commonwealth Database, 1981-1983. (Box 2)
  - Jail Reimbursement Study, 1982. (Box 3)
  - HB 199 (State Aid to Localities), 1979-1981. (Box 3)
  - Block Grants for Regional Jails / Juvenile Facilities, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Cash Management, 1979-1984. (Box 4)
  - Cash Management - Projects to Increase the Efficiency of Payments to Vendors by the Commonwealth of Virginia (Dept. of Accounts), 1983. (Box 4)
  - Cash Management - Reviews of Cash Management Practices, 1980. (Box 4)
  - Cash Management - Marine Resources Commission, 1979-1981. (Box 4)
  - Medicaid, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Moratorium on Hiring (Robb) - Executive Orders 2 and 6, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Delegation of Authority - Executive Order 37, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Executive Salary Pay Plan, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Electoral Board Study, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Energy - Coal and Energy Commission Survey on Energy, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Energy - Conversion of State Facilities from Oil/Gas to Coal, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Faculty Salary Authorization, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Fixed Asset System, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Executive Compensation Summary, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Cabinet Secretaries - Memos to, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Carillon - City of Richmond, 1982. (Box 5)
  - User Fees Study, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Reports - Integrated Transportation Network, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Reports - Revenue Bond Debt at Institutions of Higher Education, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Science and Technology Task Force, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Pre-planning, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Old City Hall purchase, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Mapping Function - State Coordination, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development (MASD) Study of Planning and Budget, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Land Use Controls - State Agencies (SB 344), 1982. (Box 5)
  - Cousteau Ocean Center, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Hay Associates - Compensation Study, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Accounts, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Dept. of Accounts - Support Requirements, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller Directives, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller Directive 2-80, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller - FIPS Project, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller - Generally accepted accounting practices, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller - Leave Accounting System, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller - Sick Pay Exclusion, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller - Miscellaneous Payroll Deductions, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller - Moving and Relocation (travel), 1983. (Box 6)
  - Comptroller - Travel Regulations, 1983. (Box 6)
  - Repayment of Working Capitol Funds, 1983. (Box 6)
  - State Internal Auditor, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - Internal Auditor, Office of, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - Minority Bank Deposits, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Appropriation Adjustment, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - UVA Sprigg Lane Dormitory, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - UVA Proposed Hostpial, 1983-1984. (Box 7)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - School of Business Advisory Board, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Virginia State University, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget Directives - Exceptions to Administration and Finance Agencies, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget Directives - Exceptions to Commerce and Resources Agencies, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget Directives - Exceptions to Education Agencies, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget Directives - Exception to Human Resources Agencies, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget Directives - Human Resources, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget Directives - Exceptions to Public Safety Agencies, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget Directives - Exceptions to Transportation Agencies, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget Directives - Exceptions to Planning and Budget, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Budget Review Session with Governor, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Federal Assistance Award Data System (FAADS), 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Federal Budget Cuts, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Budget Format, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - General Condition of Public Facilities, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Governor's Guidance Package (1982-1984), 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Governor's Guidance Package (1984-1986), 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Medicaid Analysis / Cost Containment, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Part-time Workforce Study, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget - Organization Chart, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Treasury Board, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Treasury, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - General correspondence, 1981-1982. (Box 9)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - SWC, 1981-1982. (Box 9)
  - irginia State Retirement System - Board of Trustees meetings and Committee meetings, 1982. (Box 9)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - Investment Dept., 1981-1982. (Box 9)
  - SWC - Finance Committee, 1981-1982. (Box 9)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - Finance Committee, 1982. (Box 9)
  - National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO), 1983. (Box 10)
  - National Association of State Budget Officers (NASBO) - Alternate Regional Director, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - National Governors Association, 1983. (Box 10)
  - National Tax Association - Tax Institute of America (NTA/TIA), 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - National Tax Association - Tax Institute of America (NTA/TIA) - Symposium, 1983 May. (Box 10)
  - National Tax Association - Tax Institute of America (NTA/TIA) - Board of Directors, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - National Tax Association - Tax Institute of America (NTA/TIA) - Sales and Use Taxation Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - National Tax Association - Tax Institute of America (NTA/TIA) - Meeting, 1982 Oct. (Box 10)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Payments in Lieu of Taxes, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Personnel Reports, 1979. (Box 10)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Savings Bonds, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Salary Regrades, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Senate Finance Revenue Collections, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Sheriffs Association, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Southern Governors Association (SGA), 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Salaries: College Presidents, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Southern Legislative Conference, 1982-1983. (Box 10)
  - Tax Dept., 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Treasury Board, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Treasury Board - Bonds, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Treasury Board - Ongoing, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Treasury Loans - DPT Policy, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - United Way, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Municipal League, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia State Retirement System, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - Actuary, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - Acturial Committee, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - Audit Committee, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - Board of Trustees meetings, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - Finance Committee, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - General correspondence, 1983. (Box 12)
  - Virginia State Retirement System - Investment Dept., 1983. (Box 12)
  - General Assembly, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Override General Assembly Session, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Status of 1982 Legislative Package / Fiscal Impact Statement, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Bills with no Fiscal Impact, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Legislation Coordination, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Bills / Resolutions, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Fiscal Impact Statements for Governor-Elect, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Procurement Legislation, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HJR 21 Block Grants for Jails, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Bill relating to Taxation of Certain Individuals, Corporations, Businesses and Public Companies, generally (Never introduced), 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Statement on Arts of Virginia, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Condominium Conversions, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Plan for Virginia's Disabled Citizens, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Plan for Virginia's Economic Development (1980s), 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Plan for Education in Virginia, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Plan for Energy in Virginia, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Plan for Law Enforcement in Virginia, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Governor's Management Study, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Plan for Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Proposal for Motor Vehicle Inspections, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Plan for Conservation of Virginia's Natural Resources, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - The Robb Plan for Older Virginians, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Promises, Promises, Promises, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Responsibilities of Secretarial Areas / Executive Orders 11-16, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Secretarial Roles, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - A Study of the Secrtarial System, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Placing a Ceiling on the Number of State Employees, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Preliminary Review of Tax and Budget Issues, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 31 - Capital Outlay / Revenue Bonds, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 196 - Investments in Certain Facilaties, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 197 - Deposits to State Treasury, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 414 - Transfer of Personnel Between Agencies, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 421 - Creation of Drug Investigation Special Trust Account, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 458 - Abolish Cabinet Secretaries, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 466 - Community Action Act, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 489 - Set Off Debt Collection Act, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 798 - Higher Education Bond Act, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 803 - Virginia State Retirement System, State Police, Judicial, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 804 - State Corporation Commission filing fees, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - HB 878 - Deferred Compensation Commission, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - SB 69 - Taxation of certain individuals, etc., 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - SB 198 - Block Grants / Jail Reimbursements, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - SB 213 - Annual Reports / Biennial Reports, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - SB 305 - Tax Deduction for Contributions to Certain Schools, 1982. (Box 13)
  - General Assembly - Administration and Finance Legislation, 1982. (Box 13)
- Correspondence and subject files, 1978-1984 (Accession 32883)., Extent: 8 cubic feet (8 boxes)
  - Realignments - Further Study (HJR 147), 1984. (Box 1)
  - Realignment of State Government, 1984. (Box 1)
  - Executive Reorganization, 1984. (Box 1)
  - House Appropriations Committee (HAC), 1984. (Box 2)
  - House Appropriations Committee (HAC) - Meetings, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Manpower Utilization Plan - Monthly and Quarterly Reports, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Finance Committee (Connock), 1984 Sept 13. (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Finance Committee (Connock), 1984 May 10. (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Finance Committee, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Acturarial Committee (Connock), 1984 Sept 13. (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Actuary, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Audit Committee, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Investment Committee, 1984 May 10. (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Investment Dept., 1984. (Box 2)